BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program, Inclusive: 1947-2020, undated, Bulk:1984-2017
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Biographical and Obituaries, 1947-2020, undated; 3
  - Cunningham, Donald, 2017 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Cunningham, Harold, 2002-2014 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Cunningham, Milton E., 1989-2016 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Curry, Jane, 2006-2013 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Curtis, Karen, 2007-2014 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Cutter, Richard, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Dalglish, Edward, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Daniel, Wallace, 2008-2017 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Danzeiser, E. H. Dan, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Darling, Ralph E., 2000-2017 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Davenport, Mary E., 2000-2017 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Davidson, F. M. “Cotton”, 2005-2009 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Davidson, John B., 1999-2007 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Davidson, Lorene, 2002-2013 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Davis, Derek, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Davis, Ervin, 2002-2015 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Davis, Michael G., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Davis, Roger, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Tommy, 2000-2009 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Davis, William, 2015 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dawson, R. Matt, 1992-2015 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dean, Joyce C., 2016 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Decker, Ruth, 2001-2012 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Denney, Bob, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Denney, Tila, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Denton, Robert, 1993-2008 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Diaz, Jackie, 2017 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Dickerson, Ben E., 2002-2015 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dilday, Russell, 2000-2014 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Dillard, Helen, 1998-2005 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Dixon, James W., 1992-2005 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Doak, Jim, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Dole, Malcom, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Dooley, Bill, 2017 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dougherty, Cynthia, 2012-2014 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Doty, Robert T., 2013 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - DuBois, Travis Jr., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Dudgeon, Howard, 2003-2011 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Duggin, Clara, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Duhrkopf, Richard, 2017 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Duncan, Elmer H., 2004-2009 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Dunham, Lee, 1998-2009 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Duren, Russell W., 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Dwyer, Velma, 1992-2014 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Dyer, Preston, 2008-2017 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Dyson, L. M. Jr., 2013 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Edens, Roger, 1999-2006 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Edwards, Donald, 2001-2017 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Edwards, Majorie, 2001-2016 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Eichelberger, Roland G., 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Eisenbarth, Steven, 2013-2016 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Elder, Lloyd, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Eldridge, David, 2011-2014 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Elias, Patricia, 1986-2012 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Ellis, Marc, 2012-2014 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Elzinga, Harry, 2003-2009 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Emmous, Martha, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Endres, Dianne, 2000-2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Erickson, Paul R., 2013 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ervin, Claude, 2002-2012 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fallen, Olga, 2001-2009 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fallon, Frank, 1998-2012 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Fairson, James, 2008-2017 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Farren, Elizabeth, 2011-2012 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Farris, Don, 2009-2013 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Feather, Robert O., 1980-2014 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Felice, Lawrence, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ferdon, Douglas, 1994-2015 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ferguson, Lois, 2017 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Fergeson, M. L., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Fielder, Jo, 1999-2017 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Fiedler, Zora McAnelly, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Fisher, Jo, 2006-2013 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Flanders, Tommie Lou, 1999-2011 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Flynn, John C., 1999-2009 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Foster, Effie Lu, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Foster, James O., 2011 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Foster, Tom, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Francis, Daniel, 2002-2009 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Franklin, Nellie, 1993-2012 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Fredeman, Betty Coley, 2006-2015 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Fredenburg, Karen, 2016 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Frederick, Norman H., undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Frisch, Michael, 2017 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Gaitros, Donald, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Garner, Linda, 2010-2014 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Garrett, Robert, 2013-2014 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Gatelely, Margaret, 1993-2008 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Gehlbach, Fredrick, 1995-2014 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Genrich, Sandra J., 1982-2012 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Geyer, Della, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Ghee, William, 1998-2015 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Gilbert, Ruth, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Gilbreath, Larry Kent, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Gibson, Dorothy, 2002-2010 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Gilchrest, Norman, 2001-2018 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Gilliam, Karin, 2015 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Gillum, Barbara, 2002-2009 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Gilpin, Sandra, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Githens, Elizabeth, 1992-2016 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Goebel, Marvin, 1998-2013 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Goetting, M. L., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Goforth, Thomas, 2007-2014 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Golden, Clarence C., 2003-2018 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Goode, Clement T., 1996-2015 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Goodle, Nancy R., 2000-2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Gordon, Jerry L., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gould, Yanling, 1992-2013 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Grabow, Paul, 2017 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Green, Georgia, 2017 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Gregory, Joel, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Griffin, Wilma P., 2001-2016 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Grooms, Loraine, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Guenther, Johanna, 2003-2015 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Guilbault, Sonia, 1999-2008 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Guinn, Barbara, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Hadlock, Robert, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Hafford, Delta, 1992-2013 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Hakala, Kathy Lee, 2007-2014 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Hall, Lloyd, 2007-2015 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Hall, Richard, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Haney, Edna E., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hanks, Carole, 2006-2011 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Hanks, Tom D., 2017 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Hansen, Christian, 2005-2014 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Hansma, Jack, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Hardcastle, Donald L., 2005-2016 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Harlan, Aurelia Brooks, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Harlan, William J., 2000-2017 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Harris, Edward V., 1999-2020 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Harrison, Hattie May, 1983-2001 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Harrison, Walter T. Jr., 2005-2015 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Hart, Maxine, 1981-2016 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Hartberg, Warren Keith, 2009-2014 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Harvey, Frauke, 2003-2009 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Harvey, Paul, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Harwell, Jack, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Haschke, Bernadette, 2005-2012 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Haskvitz, Alan Paul, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Hastings, Jean, 2001-2017 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Hawkins, David, 2001-2014 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Hawkins, Megan, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Hayward, O. T., 1993-2010 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Held, Colbert, 1998-2018 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Henderson, R. E., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Henke, Emerson, 1991-2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Henn, Richard L., 1993-2012 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Heritage Club, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Herring, Jack, 1993-2005 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Herrington, Mary Lee, 1999-2017 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hickey, Patricia, 1999-2011 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Hilburn, Glenn, 2001-2016 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Hillis, William, 2000-2018 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Hilton, Gracie Hatfield, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Holmes, Rod, 1992-2011 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Hopkins, Robert, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Hopper, Bunny, 2011-2016 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Hopson, Hal, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Horan, Leta, 2007-2016 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Horn, Karen, 1999-2017 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Horner, Arden, 1999-2008 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Houser, James, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Howard, Hazel, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Howard, Patricia, 1999-2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Howell, Louise Hatchett, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Howell, Robbi, 1987-2010 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Hudson, Gladys, 1998-2012 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Hughes, Sue Margaret, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Hull, Gary, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Hulme, Carolyn, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Hunt, Lucile, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Hupp, Mary Evelyn, 2009-2017 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Hurst, Fannie Mae, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Hyden, A. A., 1990-2014 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Irons, Loeen, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Isoline, Charles J., 1998-2015 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Ivie, Burl A., undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Jackson, Harold, 1989-2011 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Jackson, Richard, 2004-2016 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - James, Robert N., 2003-2009 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Jeffress, Iris P., 2010-2018 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Jeffrey, James N. “Jeff”, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Jensen, William, 2011-2017 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Jimenez, Julio, 2005-2009 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jivasantikarn, Nirund, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Johns, Baxter, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Charles D., 1977-2017 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Linda, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Marilyn, 2010-2012 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Michael, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Patricia, 2004-2012 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Pauline, 2005-2015 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Sharon, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Jones, Joyce, 2003-2017 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Madelyn, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Sara, 1978-2010 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Jonsson, Gladys, 2002-2011 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Karaffa, Ann, 2001-2013 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Karns, Phyllis, 2002-2010 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Keeth, Kent, 2003-2018 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Kemendo, Joseph, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Kemerling, David, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Kemp, Charles, 1990-2015 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Kemp, Paul Z., 2002-2012 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Keyes, Roger, 2000-2015 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Kilgore, Jack, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Kinslow, Linda, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Klaras, Vicki, 2013-2015 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Klingman, Mary, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Knopplin, David, 2003-2017 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Knue, John, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Kruschwitz, Robert B., 2016 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Kucera, Jeanette, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Kvanvig, Johnathan L., 2016 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Lake, John, 2001-2010 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Landes, James, 1986-1999 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Lane, Alta, 1999-2016 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Lane, Bill, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Lamkin, Robbie, 1998-2012 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Laugley, Ralph, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Leavell, Barbara, 1999-2005 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Lee, Lollie Lou, 1984-2007 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - LeMaster, James R., 2006-2014 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Lenox, Charlotte, 2007-2014 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Lester, Virginia, 1976-2011 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Ligon, Helen, 1999-2003 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Lind, Owen, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Linder, Marie, 1999-2014 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lindsey, Annette, 2005-2012 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Livengood, Geraldine, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Loa, Frank, 2016 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lofgren, Randy, 2014-2015 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Logan, Vernie M., 2001-2012 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Logue, Gloria, 2001-2014 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Long, Hudson E., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Longenecker, Justin, 1992-2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Longfellow, David, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Lott, Judy, 2012-2017 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Lowery, Sara, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Lucas, Patsy “Pat”, 2005-2014 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Luft, Bonnie S., 2004-2014 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Luper, Myrl, 1983-2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Lusk, Judith, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Lynn, Dorothy, 1974-2017 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Madden, Stanley C., 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Maggard, Judy, 2016 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Magnuson, Denise T., 2002-2017 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Mallet, Jerry, 2006-2009 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Malone-Mayes, Vivienne L., 2008 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Mansfield, Michael, 2008-2011 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Markham, Robert, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Martin, John, 2017 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Martin, Philip A., 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Massirer, Mary R., 2004-2010 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Mathis, Frank, 2017 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Mathis, Marie, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Matthews, Paul C., 1994-2010 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - May, William, 2017 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Mays, Edwin, 1993-2013 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Mazé, Elinor, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - McAlister, Dorothy, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - McAtee, Francis, 1992-2011 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - McBride, William E., 2001-2014 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - McBurney, Emily, 1980-2010 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - McCall, Mary, 2004-2014 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - McClanahan, John, 2010-2017 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - McCluskey, Jimmy, 2001-2009 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - McCorkle, William L., 1998-2020 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - McCullagh, Janice, 2004-2018 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - McDaniel, Jack, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - McDavid, Cecil, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - McDonald, Roger, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - McElhannon, Mary, 1998-2014 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - McEntire, Elizabeth, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - McGee, Dan, 2006-2014 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - McGregor, Wilson, 2017 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - McKeown, Ramona, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - McKinney, Joe, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - McLaughlin, Earl, 1979-2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - McNamee, L. V., 1999-2004 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - McSwain, Angus S., 1998-2011 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Menefee, Bill, 2001-2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Merlie, Melissa, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Meroney, W. P., 1927 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Merrill, Cynthia, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Miller, Ann V., 2000-2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Miller, Carol, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Miller, Eva, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Miller, Helen, 2011-2014 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Miller, Louise, 2000-2012 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Miller, Maurine B., 2004 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Miller, Ruth, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Mitchell, William, 2007-2014 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Monk, Betty Jo, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Moore, Andy J., 2003-2010 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Moore, Donald I., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Moore, Karen, 2007-2014 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Moore, Kris, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Moore, Norma, 1992-2010 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Moore, Mary, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Moore, Winfred, 2006-2015 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Morris, Brenda, 2012-2016 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Morris, Neil G., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Morris, Nell, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Morton, Mary & John, 2009-2013 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Morrow, Launa, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Moser, Leslie E., 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Muldrow, Louis, 2000-2008 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Mullins, Betty, 2002-2010 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Mungello, D. E., 2017 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Myers, Lois, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Myers, Thomas, 2012-2014 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Myre, Lela, 1998-2010 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Naud, Beverly, 2000-2017 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newland, Earl, 1998-2009 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newman, Stewart (I), 1968-1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Newman, Steward (II), 1969-1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Newsom, Tom, 2001-2011 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Nichols, Mary, 2017 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Norden, Ernest, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Norden, Janet, 2016 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Norman, Mary, 1998-2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Nowlin, Billie H., 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Nowlin, Jeanne, 2006-2009 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Nowotny, Lionel, 1999-2015 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Nunnelee, Jane, 2016-2017 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - O’Brien, Randall, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Odegaard, Thomas, 2011-2014 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Odell, Patrick, 2001-2020 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Oliver, Ben, 1947-1969 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Olson, John, 2016 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Orr, Pattie, 2017 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Ortiz, Sara, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Osborne, Harold W., 2002-2020 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Ousley, John, 1999-2010 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Oxford, Edwin, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Packard, Robert G., 2002-2016 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Pappas, Alice, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Paradis, Olga, 2007-2010 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Park, Theresa, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Parker, Don, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Parmley, Helen, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Parrish, Thomas Z., 1994-2018 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Parsons, Burke, 1959-1981 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Parsons, Joan, 1998-2012 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Patterson, Bob, 2009-2014 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Patterson, Jack, 1980-2007 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Patteson, Rita, 2016-2017 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Pennington, David, 2017 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Perry, W. C., 1980-2001 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Petty, J. William, 2017 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Piazza, Tina, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Pickett, Jan, 2009-2014 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Pickering, Lois, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Pickle, Jerry, 2008-2010 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Pinkus, A. G., 1999-2012 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Pippin, Grover “Rusty”, 2007-2014 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Pisciotta, John, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Pittman, Andrew, 2009-2015 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Piziak, Robert, 2008-2017 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Polk, Lee, 2003-2009 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Poole, Hazel Wilson, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Pope, Karen, 2015 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Porter, Euell, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Potter, Edithe, 2001-2010 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Powell, Mary, 1992-2012 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Powers, Patty, 2005-2009 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Powers, Ted, 2001-2015 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Pratt, Tom, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Prewitt, Patricia, 2002-2008 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Price, Juanita, 2000-2015 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Proctor, Thomas, 2008-2017 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Proudfit, Mary Ellen, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Purdy, Rita, 2009-2014 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Purdy, Tom, 2006-2017 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Rajaratnam, Daniel, 2010-2011 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Ramey, Diana, 2017 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Rasner, Leslie A., 1998-2017 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Ray, Robert H., 2014 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Read, Ray L., 2014-2016 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Reed, C. L., 1992-2006 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Reed, M. Ann, 2008-2012 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Reeder, Charles, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Reeser, Anabel, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Reid, Robert L., 1989-2010 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Reierson, Gerry, 1998-2018 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Rennie, Mairi, 2002-2008 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Reynolds, Joy, 2000-2014 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Rich, Wiley, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Richards, Rosemary, 2002-2012 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Ricks, Warren, 2015 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Rigby, Joyce, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Riley, Don, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Riley, Richard, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Rilgou, Barbara, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rivers, David, 2006-2010 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Robb, Alan, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Roberts, Robert, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Robertson, Martha, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Robinson, Henry L., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, Richard, 1999-2007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Vernice, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, William, 1998-2014 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Rodabough, Tillman, 2006-2014 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Rodgers, Elizabeth, 1999-2009 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rogers, Ben J., 2015 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Roller, Terry, 2016-2017 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rolf, Howard, 1984-2014 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Rose, John T. “J. T.”, 2014-2016 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Rosewell, Paul, 1998-2006 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Rosser, Catherine, 2003-2013 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Rowe, Pete, 2008-2012 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Rubio, Nieves D., 1993-1999 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Rushing, Ann E., 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Sanders, Retha, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Sanders, Rinky, 1984-2017 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Sanderson, Ethel, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Sanderson, Girvin, 1974-1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Sandford, Martha L., 2001-2016 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Sansom, Cecil Paul, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Santos, Barbara, 2002-2016 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Savoldi, Bonnie, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Schaub, G. Edward, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Schleicher, Dorothy, 2016 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Schlemmer, Beverly, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Schmeltekopf, Don, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Schreiber, Don, 2016-2017 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Schroeder, E. E. “Dutch”, 1973-2020 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Schwartze, Mark, 2005-2008 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Schwetman, Herbert, 1998-2002 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Scott, Daniel E., 2013-2017 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Scott, Richard C., 2006-2017 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Scott, Sharon, 2005-2006 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Scroggs, Howard, 1971-2012 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Sendon, Andes, 1983-2001 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Shanley, Helen, 2011-2016 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Shamburger, William, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Shanley, Richard, 2011-2016 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sharp, Avery, 2013-2015 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Shauck, Maxwell, 2008-2014 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Sheets, Janet, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Shepard, John W., 1998-2016 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Sherry, William, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Shoaf, Mary Margaret, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Shultz, Lenore, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Simmons, Harold, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Simons, Kenneth, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Sims, Michael, 2017 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Singleton, Gordon, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Skiles, Elwin, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Slater, Sheila, 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Sloan, Robert, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Slover, David, 2004-2009 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Smart, Noble, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Bernard, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Bessie Hass, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Betty B., 2012 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Calvin, 2003-2006 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Carey Ann, 2003-2016 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Cornelia M., 1993-1997 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Evelyn, 1984-2014 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Smith, George, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Smith, Gerry, 1998-2011 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Hilda, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Smith, J. B., 1979-2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Lois E., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Smith, M. A. “Catfish”, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Smith, Nell, 1998-2011 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Snow. Frances, 2000-2013 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Spain, Rufus B., 1999-2015 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Sparkman, Kathy, 2003-2016 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Spence, Bob, 2016 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Staton, Colleen Hamilton, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Staton, Ross, 1999-2018 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Stelley, Arthur F., 1998-2011 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Stephens, Eunice & W. R., 1973-2004 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Sterling, Judith, 1999-2016 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Sternberg, Felicitas, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Sternberg, Mary Jane, 1999-2015 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Stevenson, Linda, 2009-2017 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Stinson, Roddy, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Stokes, Katy, 1998-2012 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Stokes, Mitchel, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Stone, Gordon, 2010-2011 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Stovall, Stella, 1972-1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)